Guide to the Stanford University, Goldman Interschool Honors Program in Environmental Science, Technology, and Policy, Theses
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Stanford University, Goldman Interschool Honors Program in Environmental Science, Technology, and Policy, theses
1994-2004
SC4-6535
Stanford University. Goldman Interschool Honors Program in Environmental Science, Technology, and Policy.
0.5 Linear feet (16 volumes in 1 box)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Goldman Interschool Honors Program in Environmental Science, Technology, and Policy at Stanford University
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Goldman Interschool Honors Program in Environmental Science, Technology, and Policy at Stanford University
Access Terms
Environmental sciences--Study and teaching; Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Adelman, Sarah Wallace, Assessing the economic value of native bee pollination services on Yolo County wasterman farms., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Bagolino, Andrew D., First Degree Impacts of Hydrogen as a Transport Fuel: New Zealand as a Case Study., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Carrothers, T. J. [Timothy], Applying pollution prevention for organochlorine policy., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Chaplin, Rebecca Ellen, Searching for the source: how understanding habitat quality can improve marine reserve design., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Helen Y., The feasibility of recycling construction and demolition waste in Hong Kong: a look at politics, economics, and environmental impact., 1995 (Box 1)
  - Griego, Hannah R., The conservation and management of California black abalone: implications of habitat structure., 2004 (Box 1)
  - Levy, Karen, The utility of Ithomiinae (Lepidoptera: Nymphalidae) as indicators of forest disturbance: a case study of the applicability of biological research to conservation., 1995 (Box 1)
  - Lewis, Jessa, Alternatives to intensified coffee production in Costa Rica: an analysis of three more sustainable production systems., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Malk, Andrew J., Management indicator species: a critique of existing practices and recommendations for future use., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Mannor, Adi and Eric Selmon, Beyond compliance: perceptions affecting corporate envoronmentalism in the chemical industry., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Menge, Duncan Nicholas Lubchenco, Phosphorus! Or: anthropogenic global environmental changes and phosphorus limitation: interactions and implications., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Mercer, Jason, Keeping it at home: environmental altruism and Germany's ban on toxic waste exports., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Plaut, Karen, The depletion of the Ogallala aquifer: management alternatives., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Robinson, Sarah M., Of malaria and models: a biological approach to modeling breeding pools and mosquitoes for malaria transmission models., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Spencer, Kipchoge, Crazy for kilowatts: how Stanford University's voracious energy appetite is bad for business, un-green, and eminently curable., 1996 (Box 1)
  - Stewart, Vanessa Eliot-Hudson, Swedish regulation of GMOs: process, product, or politics?., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Wada, Nikolas, The impact of El Nino on the world fishmeal market., 1999 (Box 1)
- Theses, Accession ARCH.2015-039
  - Levine, Jessica, All on board? Aligning environmental sustainability and social justice in the mass transit sector. (Box 1)